(Leonard:)Your cousin Leopold.
Whom most people call Leo,
but he also answers to Lee.
(Sheldon:)Remember that, it's important.
- What's important?
- Details, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)The success or failure
of our deceitful enterprise turns on details.
- Do you have a cousin Leopold?
- No, I made him up.
(Sheldon:)I think you'd call him Lee.
(Leonard:)I don't get it. I already told her a lie,
why replace it with a different lie?
(Sheldon:)Well, first of all,
your lie was laughably transparent...
(Sheldon:)...where mine is exquisitely convoluted.
(Sheldon:)While you were sleeping,
I was weaving an un-unravelable web.
- Un-unravelable?
- Yes.
(Sheldon:)If she Googles Leopold Houston,
she'll find a Facebook page...
(Sheldon:)...an online blog
depicting his descent into drug use...
(Sheldon:)...and a desperate
yet hopeful listing on eHarmony.com.
(Leonard:)Okay, why would I go
to a drug intervention for your cousin?
Ah! Because it's in Long Beach
and I don't drive.